

Braden Gerace



Location

Newmarket, ON, L3X3B6

Phone

905 758 2394

E-mail

bra<u>dengerace@hotmail.com</u>

Date of Birth

August 2, 1995

Website:

bradengerace.github.io



- Object-Oriented Programming
- Game Development
- App Development
- Software Development
- Web Development
- Game Design
- Certification in C# and Java
- HTML, CSS, and JS
- Music Production

Summary

Game & Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in Unity and C#. Certified in C# and Java. Experienced in app development and web development. Diploma in Music Industry Arts and Certificate in Business Admin. Always striving to be better.



Work History

01/2012 -

05/2012

Recording Studio Engineer

Pezmosis Music Studio, Richmond Hill, ON

- Produced music in a professional studio with programs such as Logic and Cubase.
- Worked with artists to create their desired sound.

05/2012 -09/2013

Supervisor/Key Holder

Mucho Burrito, Aurora, ON

- Prepared food as a team in a fast-paced environment.
- Operated commercial kitchen equipment.

10/2013 -

07/2017

Cast Member

Cineplex Entertainment, Aurora, ON

- Upsold food, tickets, and merchandise.
- Customer service in-person and over the phone.

05/2018 -11/2019

Assembler

Sign of Excellence, Concord, ON

- Operated machinery to produce signs.
- Packaged and shipped large orders.

01/2020 -11/2021

Technician

Evergreen Fire & Safety, Newmarket, ON

Inspection and repair of fire extinguishers and emergency lights.



Education

06/2019 -

Unity Junior Programmer Certificate

Unity Learn - Online

12/2021 09/2016 -

Music Industry Arts Diploma

05/2018

Fanshawe College - London, ON **Business Administration Certificate**

Seneca College - North York, ON 05/2015

09/2014 -